chatblink.com 2017-03-23

# Privacy policy

chatblink is committed to protecting your personal information. Our servers are secured to protect any data you provide to us and we will never sell your contact information. In fact, the only marketing materials you will ever receive in connection with your membership to this site, are the items that you explicitly opt in to. 

In consideration of common concerns regarding the security and use of information provided on the Internet, we have created this privacy policy to inform our members precisely how any information they may provide is used. 

**Information That We Collect**  
Over the course of joining and using this website, information will be collected and stored in out database. This information includes: 

a. Account Information - Upon joining the community, users are asked to provide contact information including an email address. This is so that we can contact you regarding your membership. We do not disclose you email address to the community, nor do we sell this information to 3rd party marketing companies. 

b. Profile Information - Upon joining the community, users are asked to create a public profile which identifies themselves to the community. This may include location information such as city and province, but does not include a street address. Users also have the ability to upload photos to represent their profile to the community. All of this information is visible to anyone who visits the website, not only other members. 

c. Community Participation - During the course of participation in this community you will have the opportunity to create your own blog, initiate and respond to discussion threads, and comment on articles, book reviews, recommended restaurants, hotels, etc. Any information provided in this capacity will be visible to anyone who visits the website, not just other members. 

d. HTTP Header Information - Any time a web page is requested, your Internet browser sends standard identifying information to the Server such as your IP address, the browser you are using, and the type of Operating System you are running. All of this information is available to any website via standard Internet protocols. We use this information for statistical purposes, to better understand the demographics of our user base. We may also use IP addresses in some cases to prevent fraud. 

**Private Information**  
The following information is completely private; it will never be shared or sold: 1) Account password, 2) your email address, 3) any email addresses provided when inviting friends to join or emailing a page to a friend, or sending an eCard, 4) any correspondences between you and other members directly, 4) HTTP header information (e.g. IP Address, browser, OS). 

**Public Information**  
The following information is public and visible to anyone who may visit our website: 1) Member Profile details and photos, 2) member Blog posts, 3) Discussion forum posts, 4) Comments, including those posted to other member blogs, discussion posts, articles, and reviews. 

**Security Considerations**  
In order to ensure a high level of security, our servers are run from a secure data center, behind a firewall, with the servers and database secured. Any financial transactions are further protected by using a secured socket (SSL) for data transmission, to prevent hackers from possibly sifting the information during transit from your computer to ours. 

**3rd-Party Consideration**  
We may share public and private information with employees, consultants and 3rd party contractors in order to perform work on this community. Any time this occurs, it will be under a Non-Disclosure Agreement and with express understanding that the information is to only be used for maintaining the community.   
Separately, it should be noted that we link to 3rd party websites from this website; particularly from our advertisements and our Gifts catalog. Our privacy policy and usage terms do not apply to such 3rd party websites.   
Please note that we reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Policy Changes or Concerns**  
Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted and available on our website at the time such changes may take effect. 

Effective Date: 3/20/2013
